housejoy.in 2019-03-16

# Home

User hereinafter referred to as (“You”) and Sarvaloka Services On Call Pvt Ltd. hereinafter referred to as (“Housejoy”). Housejoy is owner and operator of www.housejoy.in (“the Website”), Housejoy’s Mobile Application for on demand home services (“Housejoy App”),collectively, including all content provided by Housejoy through the Housejoy App and the Website “Housejoy Service”

You have right not to supply personally identifiable information. If You intend to view this Housejoy Service and/or or share your data with the Housejoy Service, it is solely at your own volition, risk and after reading and confirming it to this Privacy Policy.

At the time of using the Housejoy Service you will share certain Personal Information with Housejoy, Housejoy respects your Personal Information. Such Personal Information may include your personal identifiable information such as your name, address, mobile number, your e-mail ids, your age, IP address, payment details and any other personal information which You may share in connection with the services.

When you use Housejoy’s Service through Housejoy App, Housejoy may use Your mobile device’s ID (the unique identification assigned to a mobile device by the manufacturer). Housejoy does this to store your preferences and track your use of Housejoy App. You understand and agree that Housejoy has every right to share such ID with third parties for its promotions, analysis, etc.

In case You participate in any other schemes, facilities, services provided by the Housejoy Service, You will be required to provide additional information. Such information will also remain in Housejoy’s database and will be considered as your Personal Information and will be treated as confidential.
